Hello friends, you all are having fun from this side,
today I am bringing for you
which are the
best stocks that you should check in this market which is happening
or recommended stocks from 10,000 shops and
I am going to tell you about it in the resort, so I am going to tell you the
requested to major stocks,
you should research it and
after doing the research you can buy it and I am
telling you the logical reasoning of it that they are decided to observe
to buy stocks, okay normally
you can invest as much as you want,
this Warren Buffett is the success minister, everyone
knows, what do these people do, 100% or Mishra, you will have to
stop yourself,
so the strategy that I have set is
for old stocks for a long period of time, dev by
fundamentally, I am good to say, the
freedom fighters, that we
also do research on it, plus their
buying also has to be done on international, so
if you see the charges, first you will have to do research,
you will have to do long term fold
and fundamental issues should be there from buying shares
Thumbs up, you will have to
AB your portfolio whenever you get a good opposition,
you should buy now it will say
what is the meaning of Gudda Guddi, so
here I have written on the exam that
normally if the
stock is below the Africa level, then shift it and it is a
little above from there and is
close to these people below, so this is a good time,
after a year it is going to come at the lowest of the top 10, that is, it is
coming, so at this time strike the
but subscribe
button, some of its conditions are that the stock
fundamentals should be good, if you
took a bad stop, after listening to it, you
bought it, then it can go down further, this
also happens with many people,
you should always check any of my products in recorded buy stocks without doing any process,
I always say that you should study stock
market, olive oil, whatever videos I am doing, you should take
advantage of it, do research, after that
buy people or coffee talk and
not buy all the talk, if you have a problem,
then I have given you the link of Angel Broking below,
you can open it for free by clicking on that link
This is a demat account and open a
free demat account
I will open an account in the field and in that
you will be given complete readymade research I will make
you good videos which are the
latest friend which you need to know from
investor in addition to that you download this app
in three to four pages you will get a
free demat account in it
owner of smart sps mall hey from us
free flight rs.20 brokerage personal
advisory so many benefits you can
call as per your device the
name is engine one to fatne
I have given the link download it
in this episode you might be the mother account
episode no problem but you should fry this app
my request to you is to
open an ad account by try phone
update it and see its full features
daily hundred percent satisfied and only then
you can go ahead and have fun at least we can
open free accounts episode no problem chhit
swami read which 12 stocks
which are quite mother 52nd in relax  If what you have achieved is almost
around that, then the
body black subscribed to Industries pasting,
rejected Reliance Tata company and
Industries
Ltd. 2006,
switch off good time to Bombay stock, you all will be
difficult, keep an eye on this, if the stocks are good then the
market will go down today, then someday the
sharpness will be fundamentally good,
stops are taking such, if I
can write more bed for you, then it is
fundamentally very good time, which can be
folded on long term, short
term performance may be a little up and down, I am
not doing dinner, just heart here, fundamentally very
good start, you can fold it,
okay, so these are 12 such scripts, after
shifting them, you
can think of buying in the last, you have to do detailed research about it, then
you download it
and it has a lot of speed, if you
want something restless from the company, then you
can subscribe, like turn on a very
good mode, up to 6 crores in
short term, you will get dandruff Indore your
investment record, so the last
people who have done this since 2012  Fundamentally it is a
good stock and is also giving different returns, so
if you enter such a combination then
definitely in which you will benefit but there is
one condition that you should have good holding capacity,
as many as I have told you,
Namdev Mr Rakesh Jhunjhunwala is
destroyed but you should see that his holding
capacity is very high,
Hardev Bollywood Talk, this is Tata
stock, fundamental forces are from the company, so it is
temporary, campaign was run, there is competition, there is
inflation, awards are going on from many fibers,
but someday the market will grow, then
it will give you very good returns,
okay so this is from my best staff,
you can definitely research it,
add it to your watch list, do some
research, take Enfield,
and tell me, right now
I will be your fear, the third stock is
these people, it is possible that you also
see the ground and shift around, time has bought it
and if it goes down then that can also be the
password, so you should invest your bank mode
again, now if this 50,000
investors then and  50 Ramesh, if you
call then Unit-2 is World in Power, I am
not saying that it can go down, but if it is a
fundamentally good stock, then if not today then tomorrow it will come up someday.
Now see, like when cardamom is
tested, when LIC gets IPL,
many people expected that LIC will go up so much,
but it did not open so well
and it was quite late in the afternoon. Now tell me, the cutoff for someone can
go down now, but will it perform well with these features or
not? You
think, Tata company can go down today and Mrs. today,
but what do you think, will the
fundamentalist loan company and note
record go up in the future or not, HPCL, so
I told you the name of Pooja stock, sir, very
good start, you
can go down to the levels, but
look at the oil company, if not today then tomorrow it will perform
and you should look at their 10 year record, look at the
10 year records, you understand,
but
how well the company has performed on you, so
considering all these things, do
research on the next comment,
click on the link below, you can get more
information or and you can  Take care
call that you should not ride a bike, it is
ultimately your decision, that is my job,
now I want to ride a bike and bring you the right
information in the morning, thank you so much,
if this is your first time on cell phone then
like the channel, like my video,
subscribe to the channel, press that bell icon
and if you want such
videos to reach your friends for free
then currently steering group, thank you so much, we will meet
in the next video, till then
bye